https://www.jeanniescottage.com/shop/privacy-notice-i-10.html

Contact UsMy AccountCart
Wish List
Catalog » Privacy Notice
Free Shipping
FREE shipping on orders over $75.00Continental USA only(based on item price)
Quick Find
Advanced Search
Categories
Angel Figurine GiftsAnimal Plush Toys and GiftsBaby's CornerBackpacksBeanie BabiesBirthstone GiftsBoyds Bears and FriendsCross Tea Lights by Joan Baker DesignsGardening GiftsHolidaysIbis and Orchid Wall VasesJim Shore GiftsKeychainsMiniature Glass AnimalsNight LightsNovelty GiftsPage Pals BookmarksPet Carrier PursesPicture FramesRefrigerator MagnetsTrophy Head Plush Wall MountWebkinzWild Republic Audubon Birds
Manufacturers
Please SelectA Breed ApartAdventure PlanetApplause/DakinAuroraBearingtonBoyds/EnescoBreyerCabin CrittersCarstensCascade ToysCoca-Cola InternationalConversation ConceptsCountry ArtistsDouglas Cuddle ToysE&S ImportsEnescoFolkmanisFuzzy NationFuzzy Town PlushGanzGrandmas HeartGundHansaHolbrook & CompanyIbis and OrchidJaagJJs OriginalsJoan Baker DesignKubla CraftsManhattan ToyManual WoodworkersMelissa & DougMJCNew Creative Ent.New York Toy CompanyPerfect PetzzzPlatte River TradingPurple RhinoPuzzledIncRuss BerrieSlifkaStuffed Animal HouseSwibcoTrader ImportsTrail of Painted PoniesTy Inc.UnipakUp With PaperWestland GiftwareWild RepublicWildlife ArtistsWildlife CreationsZoobiesZoology 101
What's New?
Adventure Planet Heirloom Mountain Lion $21.00
Information
Shipping & ReturnsPrivacy NoticeConditions of UseAbout Us
Secure Shopping
Privacy Notice
This Privacy Policy outlines our information gathering and usage practices for Jeannies Cottage. Its purpose is to inform you as to what personal information of yours ("User Information") is collected and how the information is used.
Jeannies Cottage does not rent, sell or lease User Information we have collected through our web site (the "Site"). We are committed to protecting the privacy and security of visitors to the Site. We do not share User Information, collected through the Site, with other third parties.
We are firmly committed to guarding the confidence you have placed in our company and to use responsibly any information that you volunteer. We strive to collect only that information we think is necessary for our legitimate business interests, such as to better understand you (our customer), to provide better service, to confirm and fulfill your order, and in connection with your potential interest in our products or business opportunities.
Information We Automatically Collect: For each web visitor, we record time of visit, IP address and browser type to analyze how visitors use our site and to gather general demographic information like country of origin, language and browser usage among our visitors. We never employ cookies to track session information and site usage patterns.
Privacy and Children: Jeannies Cottage and our web sites do not target children (defined as those persons under 13 years of age) as an audience or a market, and we do not collect information about the age of its web site users. Jeannies Cottage intends to comply with the U.S. Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998. If we learn that we have inadvertently collected personal information from a child we will make all reasonable efforts to delete that data from our records.
Shopping Cart
0 items
Sign in
Password forgottenCreate an Account
Bestsellers
01.Ganz Miniature Glass Figurine Hummingbird02.Cougar Mountain Lion Plush Keychain03.Ganz Miniature Glass Sea Turtle04.Ganz Miniature Glass Figurine Red Fox05.Ganz Miniature Glass Red Cardinal06.Ganz Miniature Glass Figurine Dragonfly07.Ganz Miniature Glass Red Crab Figurine08.Ganz Miniature Glass Figurine Blue Seahorse09.Ganz Miniature Glass Snail Figurine10.Mini Animal World Bluebird Glass Figurine
All content and Images Copyright © 2020 Jeannie's Cottage Copyright © 2000 - 2020 osCmaxPowered by osCmax v2.5.4
